《越狱》第四季 第十八集
Prison.Break.S04E18
《越狱》  前情提要
Previously on prison break.
我和将军有协议
I had a deal with the general.
你就不能让我来处理吗
You couldn just let me handle this?
如果你的处理办法就是把"锡拉"给将军
If by handle, you mean give scylla back to the general,
那就是不行
Then no.
我要提醒你  我会竭尽所能
I should warn you i'm going to do erything
来阻止你
In my power to stop you.
我只是想过自己的生活
I want my life back.
林肯  妈妈还活着
Linc, mom is alive.
你说什么
What?
看来我们会在迈阿密见面了
I guess i'll see you in miami.
如果我把"锡拉"还给将军
If i give scylla back to the general,
他会放过我和迈克尔
He leaves me and michael alone,
让我们父子平静生活
And i get to spend time with my son in peace.
如果克兰兹将军不再是个问题呢
What if general krantz were no longer in the picture?
出什么事情了
what's going on?
永别了  乔纳森
goodbye, jonathan
你在什么地方  克里斯汀娜
Where are you, christina?
我不喜欢你的口气  乔纳森
I don't like your tone, jonathan.
抱歉
Excuse me,
但现在有人想杀我
But it's been a whe since anyone's tried to kill me.
将军应该知道
The general should know by now
别来找我们的麻烦
Not to mess with us.
我不是将军派来的
The general didn't send me.
克里斯汀娜会让公司改头换面
Christina is going to change the company.
她说的是  两天后
She said after two days
她才会行动
She would make the change?
你看看那卡上的日期  两天后
Look at the date on that laminate, two days away.
我得和她谈谈
I need to talk to her.
林肯回广场了
lincoln's back at the plaza.
我警告过他不要来搅合
I told him to stay away.
请求击毙目标
we have a clean shot.
击毙
Take it.
收到
Roger that.
斯蒂文森楼顶  向后转
stevenson rooftop, 12 o'clock.
克里斯汀娜在哪里
Where's christina?!
她在哪里
Where's christina?
快点报警
Somebody call the police!
-天哪  天哪  -呆在车里
Man oh, my god, oh, my god. stay in the car.
她在什么地方
Where is she?
Where is she?!
拿到他的电话了  我们快离开
We got his phone; let's get outta here
-我们快走  -快点
We got to go. let's go.
她冬天才会来  所以...
she only uses the place in the winter, so...
我们暂时很安全
We should be fine for a while here.
那个就是黛布
and that's deb.
你们两个是大学同学吗
Were you guys in college together, too?
医学院同学
Uh, no, just medical school.
她在纽约工作
She's got a practice in new york
她每年来这里一次
And she comes down here
开研讨会
Once a year to teach a seminar.
她真不错
God, good for her.
照片照得不错
Nice family photos.
沙滩  太阳  便宜情侣装
Sand, sun, cheesy matching outfits.
我们有一天也可以像他们一样
We could have that if we wanted... someday.
验孕棒
斯图亚特  请坐
Stuart, take a seat.
"锡拉"在迈阿密
Scylla is in miami.
我们的人正在仔细搜查
Our people are combing the city as we speak.
我听说了
Yes, i've heard.
有人想造反
Someone's atmpting a hostile takeover.
现在持有"锡拉"的人
Whoever has scylla
想让所有持卡人与我对立
Is trying to turn the cardholders agait me.
鄂伦昨天还想杀我
Oren tried to kill me yesterday.
乔纳森
Jonathan...
我们卸除了你的电话
We're dumping your cell phone.
我们找到好几条
We've already found several phone calls
你和其他组织的电话联系
Between you and an unknown party.
斯图亚特  "锡拉"在谁手里
Stuart... who has scylla?
我不知道
I don't know.
好好想想
Think, buddy.
动脑子
Think.
我发誓我真的不知道
I swear i don't know anything.
我可以让你毫无痛苦地死去
This can be as painless As you want it to be.
"锡拉"在谁手里
Who has scylla?
你对这件事有点偏激了
You have gone around the bend on this.
我还没开始呢
I haven't even started yet.
林肯  这个人不是想伤你
come on, linc, this guy wasn't trying to hurt you.
他只是讨厌你的纹身
He just didn't like your tattoo.
-你真有意思  赛尔夫  -狙击手的电话记录里
You're a funny guy, self -there's a lot of calls
有个不明电话打了很多次
On the sniper's cell from a blocked number.
得让公司帮我们查
We'll need the company to help identify it.
万一是你妈的电话呢  林肯
What if it's your mom's cell phone, linc,
我们得去拜访一下
And we have to pay a visit?
你敢去吗
You got the gumption?
喂
Yeah.
林肯  我不喜欢主动打电话给你
Lincoln, i don't like having to initiate these calls.
那就别打  我们找到了再打给你
Well, don't. we'll call you when we get it.
"锡拉"在谁手里
Who has scylla?
我们不知道
We don't know,
但我们找到了一个狙击手
But we tangled with a sniper.
你们现在正在审问吗
Whom you're interrogating right now, right?
他死了
He's dead.
林肯  我们的行动目标
Lincoln, the point of this action
不是去杀人
Is not to kill as many of them as you can!
你的方法让我怀疑
Your methods make me question
你有没有能力
Whether you are capable of playing
来领导这么大的行动
On a field of this size.
我们会找到"锡拉"
We'll get scylla.
我今天就要答案
I want answers today.
你是不是有些话不敢说
Aren't you leaving something out,
一些有点敏感的话题  比如说
Something a tad critical, like it's your mom
"锡拉"就在你妈的手里
Who has scylla, hmm?
-你想多了  -那我们就谈谈
Don't think too much. let's talk about that.
是我想多了吗
Let's talk about thinking too much, okay?
你跟将军拖延时间
Are you stonewalling the general 'cause it's good
是为了我们大家  还是为了
For the team here, or are you protecting the woman
当初生你的那个女人
Who popped you out lo these many years ago, huh?
要不是克兰兹让你来  我就杀了你
If krantz didn't put you here, i'd kill you.
住手
All right, all right!
这就是我想要的答案
There's my answer.
如果告诉克兰兹"锡拉"在克里斯汀娜手里
if we tell krantz That christina has it, he may know things that'll
他要么会帮我们  要么觉得我们不再有利用价值
help us or he may determine that we're no longer useful.
大家明不明白
Everybody understand that?
我们是来找"锡拉"的  我们一定要找到
We're here to get scylla, we need scylla,
所以必须按原计划行动
And the way to do that is to stick to the plan
而且不能走漏风声
And to keep our mouths shut.
看这个
Hey, look at this.
昨天他在亚利桑那  4号公路附近的
Yesterday he found us on interstate 10,
10号洲际公路上发现我们
Near route 4 in arizona.
MS是你名字的缩写
And "ms" are your initials.
但剩下的部分就没什么头绪了
But the rest of this could mean anything.
我去查查洛克威尔然后再想办法
I'll do a search on rockwell and we'll figure it out.
假设林肯也没有什么主意
Assuming lincoln hasn't already.
他在这里三天了
He's been here three days
还有公司做后盾
And he's got access to company resources.
如果他想要什么  那他一定能的手
And once he puts his mind to something, that's it,
就算他知道他的想法是错的
Even if he figures out he's wrong.
不过  目前为止
Well, and from what i've gathered,
他还没这个觉悟
He doesn't think he is wrong,So...
如果我是"MS"  那谁是"VS"
If i'm ms, then who's vs?
孟加拉语有14个元音
Bengali has 14 different vowels.
想学会真是折磨人
It's a bitch to pronounce.
林肯跑掉了
Lincoln got away.
你看过超新星的照片吗
Have you ever seen picture of a supernova?
看过
I have.
真的很漂亮
They're quite beautiful, aren't they?
而且很少见
They're very rare; they only occur
50年才出现一次
About once every 50 years.
还有一天  我们就能目睹这样的奇观
We're a day away from a kind of supernova.
在它面前  一切都会黯然无光
A moment so powerful it'll eclipse everything.
而且没有人能阻止我
And nobody's going to stop me.
没有吗
No?
他们还没收到
They haven't got it yet.
我已经发了两次了  每次都...
Well, i've sent it twice already. either they...
收到了  收到了
They got it. they got it. okay.
帮我们调查狙击手的通话人
We need you to trace who called the sniper's cell
还有他在迈阿密的落脚点
And tell us where he is in Miami.
什么时候
Well, when?
不行
No.
完全不行  我们现在就要  我们...
Hell, no. we need it now. we...
最快一小时
Hour earliest.
什么意思  一小时
What do you mean, hour?
找到他  就能找到克里斯汀娜
We get him, we get to Christina.
妈的  通行证都准备好了
Damn well almost got our accsses hand to us getting this.
你想知道你妈的目的吗
You want to know what your mama's up to--
从那开始吧
Let's start there.
这些东西是明天用的
These things're for tomorrow.
我今天就要锡拉
I want scylla today!
那真抱歉了  小子
Oh, sorry there, sink.
我再想想吧  我的错啊
Then i go thinking again. my bad.
市区港口见  Michael
为什么
Why?
我要把你救出去
I'm getting out of here.
-是什么  -是迈克尔
- What's it?  - It's Michael.
他在迈阿密  想见面
He's in Miami, wants to meet.
什么时候
When?
不可能的
Never.
我警告过他不要来
I warned him not to come.
你好  阿历克斯
Hello, Alex.
很高兴看到你们安然无恙
Glad to see you're both in one piece.
我哥在哪
Where's my brother?
他不来
He's not coming.
你现在和他是一伙了
So you're working with him now?
是公司的人了
You work for the company?
对  没错
Sure. Fine.
你来这干吗
Why are you here?
首先想警告你
Partly to warn you.
那你就白来了
I could have saved you the trip.
因为我们要决战到底
'Cause we're seeing this thing through.
你知道些什么
What do you know?
你认为这一切是什么
What do you think you've walked into?
你来告诉我
You tell me.
你母亲
Your mother.
锡拉在她手上
She has scylla.
谁想得到它
Whoever's going to get it
都要经她的手
Has to go through her.
我要和我哥谈
I need to talk to my brother.
他不会来的
He's not coming.
他自己保命都很艰难
He's a little too busy trying
因为你的...
To stay alive because your...
你母亲要杀他
Because your mother tried to kill him.
如果你的计划不够周密
And if you stay here with some half-baked plan,
她也会来杀你
She's gonna try and kill you.
你来这干吗  阿历克斯
What are you doing here, Alex?
我想
I'm trying to get
打听点信息  任何有用的信息
Some information, anything that can help.
-要相信我  -这样你
- You need to trust me.  - So that you
就能到将军那领赏了
Can run back to the general with it?
这里的每个人
Everybody can get
都能得到自己想要的  我们不必在
What they want here. we don't have to chose between
挽救家庭和推翻公司之间选择
Saving our families and taking down the company.
可以同时做到
We can do both.
怎么做
How?
目的达成时就知道了
I'll know when we get there.
所以我请求你  拜托了
That's why i'm asking you, please,
相信我
Trust me.
你有什么消息吗
Now, do you know anything?
任何消息
Do you have anything?
我唯一能告诉你的
The only thing i can tell you is
就是我们会彻底扳倒公司
That we're gonna burn the company down to the ground,
有你没你都一样  阿历克斯
And that's with or without you, Alex.
迈克尔  关于你母亲
I'm sorry, Michael.
我很遗憾
About your mother.
昨天搞得像警察的家伙
So, the guy who was posing as a cop
肯定是我母亲的人
Yesterday must have been working for my mother.
对  我觉得你说对了
Yeah. yeah, i think you're right.
如果他接受
And if he was following
她的指令  那么
Her instructions, that means...
我猜
Guess that means
她想把我们转移到某处
She wanted the two of us transported somewhere.
至少她没想过杀我们
At least she didn't want us killed.
我应该很感激了
I guess i should be grateful.
这能改变什么吗
Does this change anything?
不能
No.
她从公司内部
The fact that she thrived
兴起并控制公司  代价却是
Within the company, at the expense of...
其他所有人的性命
Everyone else...
这让我更想扳倒公司了
...makes me want to take them down even more.
洛克威尔大街  南迈阿密
Rockwell Avenue, south Miami.
走吧
Let's go.
公司给我们的手机卡信息
All right, the SIM card information the company gave us
显示我们要找的人就在几个街区附近
Said this guy should be a couple of blocks over.
这家伙最好是
This better be the guy who
你找到的那个线索  林肯
Ordered the lead on you，Linc.
-别是什么送披萨的  -你就不能闭嘴啊
- Not some pizza delivery boy. - Why don't you just shut up?
行了  听着  他快停下了
All right, listen, he's stopping.
林肯  你再向前开4分之1英里
Lincoln, you're gonna make a right
然后向右转
About a quarter of mile up.
是什么地方
What's the location?
我也不知道  但是很大
I don't know, but it's big.
门上的印章是哪的
Whose seal is that?
印度  这里是大使馆
India. This is the embassy.
他在那呢
All right, there he is.
看谁和他一起呢
And look who he's with.
锡拉在她手里
She's got Scylla.
-我们得想办法进去  -不行
- We need to get in there. - No, no, no, no, no, no.
她进去了肯定还会出来
Okay, if she's going in, she's gonna come back out.
等她出来我们再上
And when she does, we take our shot.
我在福克斯河监狱学到的一件事就是
One thing i learned at Fox River-- just 'cause
有些东西是有去无回的
Something goes in, don't mean it always comes back out.
说的对
You're right.
说啥  再说一遍
Hark, what was that? One more time?
她现在带着锡拉
Look, she's got that thing on her.
我们必须现在行动
We need to move now.
我们得分散他们的注意力
We need to create a distraction.
准备好了吗  帝博格
Self ready to go, T-Bag?
不  你让我说什么
No, no, no, no. Well, what do you want me to say?
想到哪说到哪吧
Just run your mouth.
你知道怎么做
You know how to do that.
我们进去了就通知你
Look, when we get in, we'll let you know.
在此之前  别让他们闲着  自己想办法吧  好吧
Until then, you keep 'em busy. Figure it out,okey?
拜托  唐
Oh, come on, Don.
这我可不在行
I don't know about that.
你能行的  自己想办法
You'll be fine. Just figure it out.
打扰下
Excuse me?
打扰下  先生  我要见你们的总统
Excuse me. I'd like a meeting with your president, sir.
您能传达一下我来了吗  谢谢
Uh... Could you notify him I'm here? Thank you.
我们的总统不住美国  先生
The president doesn't live in America, sir.
她住在喀什米尔
She lives in Kashmir.
是个女的啊
She? Oh, well.
这就清楚多了  听着
That explains a lot, don't it? Listen,
老印  我不想跟你计较
Haji, I got no beefs with you, okay?
但对于一个有思想的人
It's just, there comes a point when a thinking man
必须表明自己的立场
Has to take a stand.
知道还有什么谁有思想吗  大象
You know who else thinks? Ephants.
没错  大象
That's right. Elephants.
你知道大象的大脑是
You know, they have the largest brain
整个动物王国中最大的么
In the whole animal kingdom?
你知道吗
Did you know what?
快点  巴格维尔
Come on, Bagwell.
-先生  -你们印度人一直
- Sir... - You folks have a history
不善待这种神圣的生物
Of mistreating these mighty creatures,
到现在为止  没有人站出来说话
And up till now, no one's been lifting a finger.
一直没有
Up till now.
先生  这里是私人领地
This is private property, sir.
麻烦您离开
I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
我哪也不去
Well, i'm not going anywhere.
快解开
Unlock those now!
这里是4号门卫  发生情况  代号11
This is Station Four. I have a Code 11.
来啊
Bring it!
监控摄像头现状良好
Security camera's looking good.
让他去吧
Let him go.
我们走
Let's move.
走
Go.
先生  美国领土在路的另一头
Sir? sir? America's on the other end of that sidewalk.
这里是国际领土
You're on internional soil.
出于对您的考虑  我希望你带了手铐的钥匙
For your sake, I hope you brought the keys for that.
我不跟你发牢骚  好吧
I have no-no gripes with you at all, okay?
我一直给国会议员打电话
I've been calling my Congressman.
我一直写信给联合国
I've been writing United Nations.
我不管
I don't care.
你知道大象
Did you know that elephants eat
每天要吃超过500磅重的食物吗
Over 500 pounds of food per day?!
它们的粪便
And their dung...
还可以用来... 用来做
It can be... i can be processed
用来做纸
Into parchment.
先生  你再不走可有大麻烦了
You're about to be in a big heap that, sir.
-大象  -快点来前门
- Elephant! - Front gate now.
大象
Elephant!
我们走
Let's go.
好了  开始吧
All right, let's go.
我给巴格维尔发个信息告诉他我们进来了
I'm gonna text Bagwell and let him know we're in.
911以后  国安局出台了一些
All right. After 9/11, DHS implemented some new
-新规程  -快点吧
- Protocol regarding... - Just hurry up.
真是太让人厌恶了
It's an abomination.
就是这样
That's what it is.
太让人厌恶了
It's an abomination.
为什么  因为大象  在黑猩猩之后
Why, the elephants, next to the chimps,
基因序列和人类的最相近
Have the closest DNA sequee as us human beings.
先生  你说的好像不对吧
Sir, don't think that's true.
我们进来了
不好意思打扰了
Sorry to inconvenience you guys.
车来了  伙计
Your ride's here, pal.
抓住他
Take him.
只是小误会
This is just a misunderstanding.
他们会带你
They're going to take you down
去动物园拜访你的大象兄弟
To visit your buddies at the zoo.
-巴格维尔有麻烦了  -我们被发现了吗
- Bagwell's in trouble. - Are we made?
我们快没时间了  快点
We're not waiting around to find out. let's go.
摄像头10秒内就会
We got about ten seconds
拍到我们了  快点
Before we go live all over this place. Come on.
好了  快走
Okay, here we go. let's go.
这边没什么情况
All right it looks good over here.
这里也没有
Clear here.
我们得抓紧时间
We got to hurry.
你亲眼见过泰姬陵吗
Have you ever seen the taj mahal?
只在照片上看过
Only in photographs.
你呢
You?
看过几次
several times.hs.
沙・贾汗为他的宠妻建造的
It was built by the Shah Jahan for his favorite wife.
我记得和我前夫提过此事
I remember telling that to my ex-husband.
你知道他什么反应吗
Do you know what his reply was?
克里斯汀娜  你真贴心
That's very sweet, Christina.
我很好  谢谢
I'm fine, thank you.
-请  -谢谢
- Please. - Thank you.
抱歉我设了重重警卫
I'm sorry for all the extra security,
但你一定知道
But as I'm sure you realize,
有很多人
There's a lot of people
对它都望眼欲穿
Who would like to get their hands on this.
这是太阳能电池模型概况
This is an overview of the solar cell prototype.
而这只是一个开始
That's just the beginning of what's on here.
海水淡化技术
A desalination technique
可在几秒内
That can yield potable water
产出饮用水
Within seconds.
生化农作物
Bioengineered crops
在恶劣环境中仍能生存
That will subsist in the harshest of climates.
革命性的疫苗
Revolutionary vaccines.
有谣言说这都属于
Well, you know, that there's a rumor floating about
克兰兹将军
That this belongs to general Krantz.
你夫人手上戴的
That eight-carat purple diamond
8克拉紫钻钻戒
Your lovely wife wears on her hand.
你关不关心
Did you worry out
是从南非哪国来的呢
Which south african country it was taken from?
利润我们五五分成
The profit margin would be split fifty-fifty.
制造和销售都归贵国
Your country would handle the manufacturing and distribution.
我只是你的隐秘合伙人
I would act as your silent partner.
请坐
Please.Have a seat.
最后一着  准备好了吗
Last resort. We clear?
他还没准备好
No, he's not clear.
我们在这里开枪
We fire off a shot in here,
就没有退路
Not getting out.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
明白
We're clear.
我觉得你对我隐瞒了什么
I sense there's something that you're not telling me.
你只需要
All you have to do
出席明天的先进能源大会
Is show up at the progressive energies conference tomorrow,
登上讲台
Go up on the dais,
亲自展示这项技术
And present this technology as your own.
万一大会失败
So, I'm the one
我就是那个出丑的人
Who looks like the fool if this venture fails.
各国的首脑
The leading minds of this world
都会参加明天的大会
Will be at that conference tomorrow,
着眼于地球上
Working on the crisis
的能源危机
That we are facing with our planet.
你将是那个可以给出答案的人
You will have the solution.
你会是梦想的化身
You will be a visionary.
文森特・桑登斯基博士
Dr. Vincent Sandinsky
在相关科学领域
Has done extensive research
做了大量的试验
On the bargain theory.
证明这在实际应用方面
Says that proof of its practical application
结果非常不稳定
Is pretty shaky.
他会在明天的大会上做报告
He's givina lecture tomorrow at the conference
我要确保我们走下台前
And I'd like to make sure that his findings
我们的项目
Don't debunk the foundation of our project
不会被他揭穿
Before we even get off the ground.
纳威
Naveen,
我现在向你提供的技术
The technology that I am offering you
会让你的国家
Will catapult your country
比现在先进50年
50 years ahead of its time.
当然
Naturally,
有别的国家也很感兴趣
A few other countries have expressed some interest.
我相信几年之后
I'm sure that they would be happy
他们会以三倍的价格
To sell you this information
出售这些信息给你
At three times the price in a few years.
你来得太突然了
This is all very sudden.
我说过我也是最近才得到的
Well, as I said, I only acquired this recently.
但我向你保证很快就会出售
But I assure you, it is going to sell.
出于对你父亲的尊重  我才先找你
I came to you first out of respect to your father.
我只再说一句话
I will just say one more thing...
然后由你自行决定
Then I will let you do what you like.
你父亲面对这笔交易
What do you think your father
会作何定夺
would have done with this offer.
桑登斯基将于下午四点半到达
请给我一分钟时间
I need a minute.
不用为桑登斯基担心
And don't worry about Sandinsky.
我们会搞定他
He won't be a problem.
这里是洛克威尔路48号
This is 48 Rockwell.
我们要找B23车位
We need B23.
那里是D开头的
Row D.
B开头的在那里
Row B.
这就是B23
B23. this is it.
费尔南多教了你不少东西啊
Fernando was a great influence on you, huh?
我也教了他不少
And vice versa.
找到了
Here we go.
车钥匙
Car keys.
没有行程表
So, there's no itinerary,
但有一张标记去达埃弗格雷兹纪念机场的地图
But we do have a map to the Everglade Memorial Airport.
还有一把枪
And we have a gun.
我一直有这个想法
I've been thinking about this.
VS是某人名字的缩写
"V" and "S" are someone's initials.
1630在军方术语中是下午四点半
1630 is 430 p.m. military time.
如果不是我们要找的人离开
What if our guy wasn't flying out,
而是有个名叫VS的人正赶过来呢
But someone named VS was flying in.
发现一个我们要找的人
I found one of our guys.
很好  他会带我们找到克里斯汀娜
Good. he'll take us to Christina.
-你在什么位置  -2楼
- Now where are you?  - Second floor.
靠近大厅处
Near the atrium.
不许动
Don't move!
别动
Freeze!
23号  抓到林肯・布伦斯了
23, I have Lincoln Burrows
还有另外2名男性疑犯
and two male suspects in custody.
我们得赶紧离开
We need to clear out.
怎么了
Excuse me?
林肯在这里
Lincoln's in the building.
我得完成这笔交易
I need close this deal.
而不是像个外行一样
Preferably without looking like an amateur.
处理好
Handle it.
进去
Get in there.
快走
Move!
跪下
Get on your knees,
双手抱头
Put your hands on your head.
跪下
Get down.
呼叫318
318.
明白
Understood.
敢动一下
Move an inch
我就毙了你们
And I won't hesitate to kill any of you.
我已经做好决定了
I think we've come to a decision.
你负责履行你的那部分协议
You honor your side of the agreement
我则会在明天会议上公开
And I will do the unveiling at the conference tomorrow.
纳威  真是个好消息  好消息
That's great news, Naveen. great news.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
我们走
Let's go.
还有别的路出去吗
Is there another way out of here?
他让我们不要靠近门
He just said don't go near the door.
这里是大使馆
This is an embassy.
克里斯汀娜跟我们一样不想出岔子
Christina can't risk an incident, just like we couldn't.
没有人会杀我们
Nobody's going to kill us.
我们走
Let's go.
我不知道他们是如何找到我们的
I don't know how the hell they found us.
我现在只关心桑登斯基
All I care about is Sandinsky.
莫里斯上路了吗
Is Morris on his way?
我们还没有收到他的消息
We haven't heard from him yet.
我会查查他的情况
I'll check his status.
把电话给我
Here, give me that.
你们跟谁一起来的
Who are you gentlemen with?
克里斯汀娜
Christina.
给
Here.
她落下的
She dropped this.
桑登斯基将于下午四点半到达
还有大概一英里远
We're about a mile away.
你的电话吗
Is that you?
应该是手提箱里的
I think it's coming from inside the briefcase.
私人来电
Private caller.
他们能通过手机追踪到我们吗
Can they track us on this thing?
开免提
Put it on speakerphone.
喂
Hello?
迈克尔
Michael?
是你妈妈吗
Was that your mom?
迈克尔  我很遗憾
Oh, Michael, I'm so sorry.
我不知道该说些什么
I don't even know what to say.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to say.
什么都不用说
Nothing at all.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
锡拉在哪
Where's scylla, huh?
他们在我们得手前离开了
They left before we could get it.
我都快把命搭上了
I got the ass kicking of a lifetime
你们却空手回来了
And you come back empty-handed?
我们拿到了这个
We got this.
就一张便签纸
A post-it note?!
你们就弄到了这个
That's what you got?
你们怎么不弄点
How about some elmer's glue?
埃尔默胶水
Did you get any of that?
你冷静点
Would you calm down.
这个对于我们很重要
This is important to us.
如果我们告诉将军
If we had just told the general...
就告诉将军吧
Just told the general...
再试一次
One more time.
如果这个人对于克里斯汀娜很重要
Hey, if this guy's important to Christina,
那么他对于我们也很重要
He's important to us.
给公司打电话  查一下这个人
Hey, let's call the company, get a read on him.
我去办
I'll do it.
-你还好吗  -我很好
- You all right? - Yeah, i'm good.
我马上就出来
I'll be right out.
无论VS是谁
Whoever VS is,
他的航班将在30分钟内抵达
Their plane gets in in less than 30 minutes.
我们得查一查航班记录
We need to get our hands on that flight log.
打扰一下  我听说
Um, sorry, i notice you have
你们这可以报名学开飞机
A sign up there that says I can learn to fly here.
你们有没有宣传册让我看看
Do you have a brochure I can take a look at?
我回头打给你
Let me call you back.
当然  我给你找找
Sure, I should have one around here somewhere.
谢谢  麻烦你了
Thank you. sorry.
给你
There you go.
学习如何飞行
"learn how to fly."
太好了
Is is perfect!
迈克尔
Michael.
洗手间那有个出口
There was an exit by the bathrooms.
再给我30秒
I need 30 seconds.
如果被他们发现  我们就死定了
They will kill us if they find us.
文森特・桑登斯基
Vincent Sandinsky.
VS  N727MG航班
VS. N727MG.
我们走
Let's go.
明白
Got it.
文森特・桑登斯基现正在飞机上
Vincent Sandinsky's on a plane right now.
现正飞往达埃弗格雷兹纪念机场
He's heading into everglades memorial airport.
我们有15分钟时间
We got 15 minutes
要赶到劳德代尔堡
To get to fort lauderdale.
如果堵车  就赶不上了
With traffic, there's no way we're going to make it.
那你就呆在这
Then stay.
有什么需要帮忙的吗
Excuse me, can I help you?
你说呢
Funny you should ask.
我要让你告诉指挥塔
I need you to call up to the tower
给N727MG航班传信息
With a message for N727MG.
N727MG航班
N727MG.
这里是埃弗格雷兹纪念机场指挥中心
This is everglade memorial tower.
据另一架飞机报告
We just got word from another craft
你们的左舷涡轮冒黑烟
That your port side turbine's trailing black.
指挥塔  N727MG收到
Tower, I'm clear across the board here.
现在可以降落吗
Am I still good for landing?
告诉他们
Now tell them he needs to land
按照紧急情况协定
At the north end of the tarmac
在停机坪的北侧降落
And follow emergency protocol.
-那会...  -快说
- But that'll... - tell them.
是否收到
Do you copy?
指挥塔  这里是指挥中心
Tower, this is operations.
让N-7
Have november-seven-
2-7-M-G航班从西南方向降落
Two-seven-michael-golf approach from the southwest.
我们不能冒任何风险
We're not gonna take any chances.
我们会派人去接应
We're gonna send a crew out to them.
飞机着陆马上疏散乘客
Have the passengers evac as soon as they hit the ground.
收到
Roger that.
通知安保部门
Now call down to security.
送莎拉・唐克雷蒂医生去停机坪
Tell them Dr. Sara Tancredi needs to be let on the tarmac.
有一位乘客
One of your passengers has had
突发心脏病
A heart attack.
需要立即提供帮助
He needs immediate assistance.
安保部门  这里是指挥中心
Security, this is operations.
再过一分钟
One more minute,
我就会离开
And I'll be out of your hair.
老兄  你会因此惹上大麻烦
You could be getting in big trouble for this, guy.
会进监狱的
You could go to prison.
进哪个
Which one?
有情况
Something's going on here.
你是文森特・桑登斯基吗
Vincent Sandinsky?
什么事
Yes?
您好  我是唐克雷蒂医生
Hi. Dr. Tancredi.
您得跟我走一趟
Sir, i need you to come with me.
出什么事了
Is there something wrong?
我们担心您在飞行过程中
Uh, we have some concerns about some health exposure
可能出现一些健康问题
You may have experienced during the flight.
-对不起  -走吧
- I'm sorry, I don't...  - Let's go.
这位是迈克尔・斯科菲尔德
Michael Scofield,
这位是文森特・桑登斯基
Vincent Sandinsky.
快上车
Get in the car.
-为什么  -坐后面
- Why...  - Back seat.
快上车
Get in!
求求你
Please...
别伤害我
Don't hurt me.
我不会伤害你
I won't.
但是他们会
But they will.
你们要什么我都给
You can take everything I have.
求求你们放了我
Just... please let me go.
你认识克里斯汀娜・斯科菲尔德吗
Do you know who Christina Scofield is?
谁  不认识
Who? No.
迈克尔  前面没路了
Michael, I'm running out of road.
往飞机棚那开
Head for the hangars.
天哪
Oh, my god.
My god, oh, my god.
出什么事了
What's going on here?
下车
Get out of the car!
马上
Now!
-迈克尔  -下车
- Michael...  - Get out of the car!
-天哪  -快点
- Oh, my god, oh, my god.  - Move it!
-照他们说的做  -快点
- We should do wh they say.  - Move it!
趁他们还没杀我们之前
Come on, before they kill us.
照他们说的做吧
Let's just do what they want.
趁他们还没杀我们照做吧  拜托
Let's just do what they want before they kill us, please.
跪下
Get down.
快点跪下
Get down now!
快点
Now.
让他回车里
Put him in the car.
这两个人要怎么解决
What do we do with these two?
杀了他们
Kill them.
你们没事吧
You okay?
多亏了你们
Thanks to you, I guess.
下车
Get out.
快点下车
Here, move it.
-要带我去哪  -快走
- Where are you taking me? - Move.
-出什么事了  -快走
- What's going on? - Go, move!
-要带我去哪  -快走
- But where are you taking me? - Move it!
你们想干什么
What do you want to do with me?
少废话  快走
Come on, stop talking and start walking.
你这么做是错的
This is a mistake.
林肯  你疯了吗
Lincoln, have you lost your mind?
出什么事了
But... what's going on?
快上车
Just get in the car now.
你下一步准备干什么
What are you gonna do?
打死我吗
Shoot me?
迈克尔  我警告过你别来
I warned you not to come, Michael.
我这么做是为了我们这个家
I'm doing this for us, the family.
不会就这么结束的
Well, it's not over.
绝对不会
Not by a long shot.
什么事
What?
我手头有一些信息
I... got some information for you.
不过我要确保我们所说的一切
But I want to make sure that everything
依然对我有利
We talked about is still heading my way.
车子  办公室
The car, the office
还有房子
And the house.
巴格维尔  如果你想耍我的话
Bagwell, if you're jerking me around...
你还想不想谈
You trying to talk me out of it?
别废话
Just tell me.
是林肯和迈克尔的老妈
Linc and Michael's mother.
锡拉在她手里
She's got scylla.
她在迈阿密
Here in Miami.
将军
And, general...
准备一架飞机
Fuel the jet.
去迈阿密
We're going to Miami.
克里斯汀娜・露丝・斯科菲尔德
Christina Rose Scofield.
你听过这个名字吗
That name mean anything to you?
没有
No.
那她怎么会有你的行程资料
Then why was she holding on to your flight information?
我不知道
I have no idea.
你有听过公司吗
You ever heard of the company?
也没有
No.
-公司  -你从来没有听说过公司
- Company!  - You never heard of the company?
听说过"锡拉"没有
You ever heard of scylla?
你是干什么的
What do you do for a living?
我是达特茅斯学院的教授
I'm a professor at dartmouth.
来迈阿密做什么
What are you doing in miami?
我...只想离开新罕布什尔
I, uh... i just wanted to get out of new hampshire
一段时间
For a few days.
老实说  现在
To be honest, right now...
我倒希望没来
I wish i hadn't.
放松
Just relax.
我接到组委会的电话
I got a call from the organizing committee
来此参加明天的先进能源会议
Of the progressive energies conference that's here tomorrow.
他们说如果我能做个报告
They said they would fly me out
他们会来接我
And put me up in a hotel
送我去宾馆
If i gave a short presentation.
你电话在哪
Where's your cell?
在我上衣里
Uh... it's-it's in my jacket.
为什么对我撒谎
Why are you lying to me?
我下飞机时还在身上
I had it when i got off the plane.
我向上帝发誓
I swear to god.
迈克尔  他说他不认识你妈
Yeah, Michael, he said he doesn't
但他们之间
Know your mom, but there's got to be
来往有20封邮件呢
20 e-mai back and forth between them.
他们不仅认识彼此
They don't just know each other.
还一起做事
They're working together.
问题是  做什么
The question is, on what?
林肯
Linc.
文森特・桑登斯基
Vincent Sandinsky.
最后一个来电好吗是什么
What about the last number dial there?
那个号码打来很多次
There's a lot of calls from that number.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
怀孕检测：阳性
有消息吗
Anything?
还没有
not yet.
喂
Yes?
他对你有多重要  妈妈
How badly do you want him, mom?
迈克尔  听我说
Michael, listen to me.
这不是答案
That's not an answer.
我会再给你电话
I'll be in touch.
他说的是真的
His story checks out.
但还有些事
Listen, there are still some things
我们需要查  一旦查清了
We need to figure out, but as soon as we do,
就放你走
We'll let you go.
谢谢
Thank you.